Midtown Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs, circa 1925-circa 1980, Series 6:; (6.5 linear feet)
  - Works of Art, A-Z, 6.2:
    - Cooke, Alvin, (35-mm color slides) (Reel [unfilmed])
    - Copley, John Singleton (Reel 5416, Frame 687-690)
    - Corcos, Lucille (Reel 5416, Frame 691-711)
    - Courbet, Gustav (Reel 5416, Frame 712-715)
    - Crawford, Alice Berle (Reel 5416, Frame 716-725)
    - Criss, Francis (Reel 5416, Frame 726-739)
    - Cropsey, Jasper F. (Reel 5416, Frame 740-743)
    - Custer, Bernardine (Reel 5416, Frame 744-772)
    - Dali, Salvador (Reel 5416, Frame 773-776)
    - Da Vinci, Leonardo (Reel 5416, Frame 777-780)
    - Davis, Floyd M. (Reel 5416, Frame 781-784)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore (Reel 5416, Frame 785-870)
    - De Groot, Adelaide (Reel 5416, Frame 871-881)
    - Dehn, Adolf (Reel 5416, Frame 882-885)
    - Deineka, Aldexandre (Reel 5416, Frame 886-889)
    - Derain, Andre (Reel 5416, Frame 890-893)
    - Dolnick, Beej (Reel 5416, Frame 894-899)
    - Eisendrick, Suzanne (Reel 5416, Frame 900-903)
    - Esner, Arthur (Reel 5416, Frame 904-907)
    - Etnier, Stephen (Reel 5416, Frame 908-911)
    - Etting, Emlen (Reel 5416, Frame 912-917)
    - Evergood, Philip (Reel 5416, Frame 918-958)
    - Feigen, Dorothy (Reel 5416, Frame 959-970)
    - Ferber, Herbert (Reel 5416, Frame 971-1002)
    - Fiene, Ernest (Reel 5416, Frame 1003-1192)
    - Fitsch, Eugene (Reel 5416, Frame 1193-1202)
    - Fraser, Carol H. (Reel 5416, Frame 1203-1214)
    - Freedman, Maurice (Reel 5416, Frame 1215-1227)
    - Gainsborough, Thomas (Reel 5416, Frame 1228-1234)
    - Ganso, Emile (Reel 5416, Frame 1235-1238)
    - Gash, Chester Alan (Reel 5416, Frame 1239-1244)
    - Gauguin, Paul (Reel 5416, Frame 1245-1248)
    - Gershwin, George (Reel 5416, Frame 1249-1252)
    - Giacomantonio, G. (Reel 5416, Frame 1253-1256)
    - Glinsky, Vincent, (35-mm color slides) (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Goodman, Bertram (Reel 5416, Frame 1258-1264)
    - Grosline, Douglas (Reel 5416, Frame 1265-1268)
    - Guston, Philip (Reel 5416, Frame 1269-1343)
    - Hale, Nathan Cabot (Reel 5417, Frame 2-70)
    - Harkavy, Minna (Reel 5417, Frame 71-134)
    - Hine, Eleanor (Reel 5417, Frame 135-140)
    - Hofer, Karl (Reel 5417, Frame 141-144)
    - Hofman, Hans O. (Reel 5417, Frame 145-168)
    - Huntington, Margaret (Reel 5417, Frame 169-187)
    - Hutchinson, Mary (Reel 5417, Frame 188-193)
    - Ichikawa, Etsuya (Reel 5417, Frame 194-212)
    - Johnson, David (Reel 5417, Frame 213-216)
    - Kallis, Mischa (Reel 5417, Frame 217-219)
    - Kanelba (Reel 5417, Frame 220-229)
    - Katz, Ethel (Reel 5417, Frame 230-235)
    - Kester, Lenard (Reel 5417, Frame 236-249)
    - Kingman, Dong (Reel 5417, Frame 250-578)
    - Klotz (Reel 5417, Frame 579-586)
    - Koerner, Henry (Reel 5417, Frame 587-831)
    - Kormendi (Reel 5417, Frame 832-835)
    - Kroth, Richard (Reel 5417, Frame 836-839)
    - Lahm, Reneé (Reel 5417, Frame 840-876)
    - Laning, Edward (Reel 5417, Frame 877-915)
    - Laufman, Sidney (Reel 5417, Frame 916-919)
    - Lehman, Irving (Reel 5417, Frame 920-923)
    - Leigh, W. R. (Reel 5417, Frame 924-928)
    - Lenk, Frank (Reel 5417, Frame 929-932)
    - Lensen, Michael (Reel 5417, Frame 933-940)
    - Lhermitte, Leon Augustin (Reel 5417, Frame 941-944)
    - Lockwood, Ward (Reel 5417, Frame 945-948)
    - Lopez, Albert Varga (Reel 5417, Frame 949-952)
    - Luka, Madeline (Reel 5417, Frame 953-956)
    - Maldarelli, Oronzio (Reel 5417, Frame 957-1245)
    - Margulies, Joseph (Reel 5417, Frame 1246-1251)
    - Martin, Fletcher (Reel 5417, Frame 1252-1281)
    - Martin, Fletcher, cont. (Reel 5418, Frame 5-109)
    - Mason, Nan (Reel 5418, Frame 110-113)
    - Matisse, Henri (Reel 5418, Frame 114-117)
    - Mechau, Frank (Reel 5418, Frame 118-158)
    - Meltsner, Paul R. (Reel 5418, Frame 159-202)
    - Meyer, Fred (Reel 5418, Frame 203-206)
    - Miccoli, Arnaldo (Reel 5418, Frame 207-218)
    - Miles, Lou [target incorrectly reads Leo] (Reel 5418, Frame 219-222)
    - Miller, Kenneth Hayes (Reel 5418, Frame 223-228)
    - Miyamoto, Kaname (Reel 5418, Frame 229-236)
    - Mock, Gladys (Reel 5418, Frame 137-250)
    - Moller, Hans (Reel 5418, Frame 251-260)
    - Mommer, Paul (Reel 5418, Frame 261-300)
    - Monticelli (Reel 5418, Frame 301-310)
    - Nagler, Edith (Reel 5418, Frame 311-328)
    - Nagler, Fred (Reel 5418, Frame 329-346)
    - Nichols, Dale (Reel 5418, Frame 347-350)
    - Osborn, William (Reel 5418, Frame 351-354)
    - O'Toole, C. (Reel 5418, Frame 355-358)
    - Palmer, William C. (Reel 5418, Frame 359-366)
    - Paradise, Phil (Reel 5418, Frame 367-370)
    - Parsons, Lloyd (Reel 5418, Frame 371-382)
    - Peale, Charles Willson (Reel 5418, Frame 383-386)
    - Peirce, Alzira (Reel 5418, Frame 387-413)
    - Peirce, Waldo (Reel 5418, Frame 414-749)
    - Peirce, Waldo, Vol. 1 album, circa 1927-1935 (Reel 5418, Frame 750-776)
      (mainly photographs of paintings by Waldo Peirce, many annotated with five digit numbers (negative numbers) and some with names and addresses, possibly photographers or purchasers)
    - Peirce, Waldo, Vol. 2 album, as described above, circa 1925-1930s (Reel 5418, Frame 777-848)
    - Pickens, George (Reel 5418, Frame 849-854)
    - Pittman, Hobson (Reel 5418, Frame 855-858)
    - Poussin, Nicolas (Reel 5418, Frame 859-862)
    - Provensen, Alice (Reel 5418, Frame 863-875)
    - Puccinelli, Raimondo (Reel 5418, Frame 876-879)
    - Puvis de Chavannes (Reel 5418, Frame 880-883)
    - Reinhardt, Siegfried (Reel 5418, Frame 884-954)
    - Reiss, Lionel S. (Reel 5418, Frame 955-976)
    - Rembrandt (Reel 5418, Frame 977-980)
    - Renoir, Pierre Auguste (Reel 5418, Frame 981-987)
    - Ribot, Auguste Theodule (Reel 5418, Frame 988-991)
    - Rosenthal, Doris (Reel 5418, Frame 992-1213)
    - Saarinen, Lilian Swann (Reel 5418, Frame 1214-1301)
    - Saarinen, Lilian Swann, cont. (Reel 5419, Frame 5-54)
    - Saul [Berman] (Reel 5419, Frame 55-68)
    - Sawyer, Helen (Reel 5419, Frame 69-71)
    - Scaravaglione, Conceta (Reel 5419, Frame 72-78)
    - Scheffel, H. H. (Reel 5419, Frame 79-82)
    - Schein, Eugenie (Reel 5419, Frame 83-91)
    - Schoener, Jason (Reel 5419, Frame 92-97)
    - Sepeshy, Zoltan (Reel 5419, Frame 98-362)
    - Shulkin, Anatol (Reel 5419, Frame 363-433)
    - Signac, Paul (Reel 5419, Frame 434-437)
    - Simkhovitch, Simka (Reel 5419, Frame 438-451)
    - Simpson, Martha (Reel 5419, Frame 452-470)
    - Singer, Susi (Reel 5419, Frame 471-476)
    - Sivard, Robert (Reel 5419, Frame 477-480)
    - Skolfield, R. (Reel 5419, Frame 481-484)
    - Smith, Jacob Getlar (Reel 5419, Frame 485-490)
    - Sokole, Miron (Reel 5419, Frame 491-541)
    - Soyer, Isaac (Reel 5419, Frame 542-591)
    - Spagna, Vincent (Reel 5419, Frame 592-608)
    - Spruce, Everett (Reel 5419, Frame 609-612)
    - Stave, George (Reel 5419, Frame 613-616)
    - Stern, S. Tilden (Reel 5419, Frame 617-631)
    - Stewart, Robert (Reel 5419, Frame 632-635)
    - Stillman, Ary (Reel 5419, Frame 636-647)
    - Taubes, Frederic (Reel 5419, Frame 648-747)
    - Thon, William (Reel 5419, Frame 748-797)
    - Utrillo, Maurice (Reel 5419, Frame 798-803)
    - Valentine, Edward (Reel 5419, Frame 804-813)
    - Van Gogh, Vincent (Reel 5419, Frame 814-817)
    - Varga, Margit (Reel 5419, Frame 818-821)
    - Veber, Jean (Reel 5419, Frame 822-825)
    - Vickrey, Robert (Reel 5419, Frame 826-831)
    - Vidar (Reel 5419, Frame 832-843)
    - Vry (Reel 5419, Frame 844-849)
    - Vuillard, Edouard (Reel 5419, Frame 850-855)
    - Vukovic, Marko (Reel 5419, Frame 856-929)
    - West, Benjamin (Reel 5419, Frame 930-933)
    - West, Bernice (Reel 5419, Frame 934-9956)
    - Whittredge, Worthington (Reel 5419, Frame 957-960)
    - Wingate, Arline (Reel 5419, Frame 961-1018)
    - Winters, Denny E. (Reel 5419, Frame 1019-1934)
    - Wolfson, Paula (Reel 5419, Frame 1035-1038)
    - Young, E. Helen (Reel 5419, Frame 1039-1042)
    - Zorach, William (Reel 5419, Frame 1043-1081)
    - Unidentified Paintings (Reel 5419, Frame 1082-1110)
    - Unidentified Sculpture (Reel 5419, Frame 1111-1144)
    - Midtown Artists [original collation in album (most unidentified)] (Reel 5419, Frame 1145-1152)
    - Draper Collection (Reel 5419, Frame 1153-1188)
    - Hauth Collection (Reel 5419, Frame 1189-1214)
    - Michener Collection, A-Z by artist (Reel 5419, Frame 1215-1249)
    - Perutz Collection, A-Z by artist (Reel 5419, Frame 1250-1260)
    - Purchased with William H. Wise (Reel 5419, Frame 1261-1282)
    - Illustrations for Painting in the U.S.A. by Alan D. Gruskin (Reel 5419, Frame 1283-1348)
    - Illustrations for Painting in the U.S.A. by Alan D. Gruskin, cont. (Reel 5420, Frame 5-78)
    - Paintings sold and gifts, undated (Reel 5437, Frame 418-445)
    - Works of art, undated (Reel 5437, Frame 446-457)
    - European paintings, undated (Reel 5437, Frame 458-483)
  - Exhibitions, A-Z, and Unidentified, 1939-1972, undated, 6.3:
    - Alley Galleries [Midtown Artists], 1971 (Reel 5420, Frame 79-81)
    - Art In Interiors, 1952 (Reel 5420, Frame 82-93)
    - Art In Interiors, 1953 (Reel 5420, Frame 94-97)
    - Art In Interiors, 1956 (Reel 5420, Frame 98-106)
    - Art In Interiors, 1957 (Reel 5420, Frame 107-116)
    - Art In Interiors, 1960 (Reel 5420, Frame 117-124)
    - Art In Interiors, 1961 (Reel 5420, Frame 125-132)
    - Art In Interiors, undated (Reel 5420, Frame 133-307)
    - Barabbas, 1962 (Reel 5420, Frame 308-325)
    - Bristol [R.I.] Art Museum, undated (Reel 5420, Frame 326-329)
    - Burdine's Department Store (Ft. Lauderdale, Fla.), 1960 (Reel 5420, Frame 330-341)
    - Carnegie Institute, 1948-1949 (Reel 5420, Frame 342-355)
    - Central Illinois Art Exposition (Bloomington, Ill.), 1939 (Reel 5420, Frame 356-359)
    - Midtown Galleries at New York World's Fair, 1965 (Reel 5420, Frame 360-368)
    - Midtown Galleries 40th Anniversary, 1972 (Reel 5420, Frame 369-372)
    - Midtown Galleries, San Francisco, 1946 (Reel 5420, Frame 373-375)
    - Onondaga Silk Co., 1946-1947 (Reel 5420, Frame 376-429)
    - Rockefeller Home Center (Kansas City), undated (Reel 5420, Frame 430-443)
    - Squibb Gallery, undated (Reel 5420, Frame 444-447)
    - Upjohn Collection, undated (Reel 5420, Frame 448-485)
    - Unidentified exhibitions [at Midtown Galleries?], undated (Reel 5420, Frame 486-498)
  - Miscellaneous, A-Z, 1943-1969, undated, 6.4:
    Miscellaneous subjects are arranged alphabetically by name or subject.
    - Binford, Julien (costumed model, and views of property owned by the artist) (Reel 5420, Frame 501-514)
    - Converse Art Gallery interior, and exterior of Slater Building (separated from Isabel Bishop letter dated Feb. 20, 1969), circa 1969 (Reel 5420, Frame 515-518)
    - Gruskin's Department Store (Reel 5420, Frame 519-522)
    - Koerner, Henry (male model) (Reel 5420, Frame 523-526)
    - Moller, Hans (cottage at Monhegan, Maine) (Reel 5420, Frame 527-530)
    - Peirce, Waldo (unidentified people, possibly Peirce's friends, boat, and views of Maine coast) (Reel 5420, Frame 531-539)
    - Rosenthal, Doris (models, mainly children) (Reel 5420, Frame 540-553)
    - Shiloh Baptist Church (Reel 5420, Frame 554-598)
    - Shulkin, Anatol (views of the Soviet Union, including 4-16mm color motion picture films that are unfilmed) (Reel 5420, Frame 599-653)
    - Thon, William (nature pictures and texture studies from The Artist and His Technique by Alan D. Gruskin) (Reel 5420, Frame 654-684)
    - U.S. Navy, Frontiline Medical Aid, 1943 (Reel 5420, Frame 685-694)
    - Fashion Models at Midtown Galleries, 1952 (Reel 5420, Frame 695-701)
    - Window Displays featuring Midtown Artists, 1952, 1957, undated (Reel 5420, Frame 702-722)
  - Negatives, 6.5:
    - People, A-Z (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Works of Art, A-Z, and Unidentified (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Exhibitions, A-Z (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Miscellaneous, Shulkin photos of the Soviet Union (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
- Printed Matter, 1932-1990, undated, Series 7:; (7.25 linear ft.)
  7.1: Printed Matter Produced by Midtown Gallery, 1932-1983, undated
  7.2: Clippings, Artist Files
  7.3: Clippings of Midtown Gallery Exhibitions, A-Z, 1932-1982, undated
  7.4: Miscellaneous Clippings Regarding Midtown Galleries and the Gruskins, 1932-1990, undated
  - Printed Matter Produced by Midtown Gallery, 1932-1983, undated, 7.1:
    This subseries (1 linear foot) consists of exhibition catalogs, 1932-1983, news releases, 1935-1983, and Midtown News, 1965-1970, a brief newsletter issued sporadically.
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1932 (Reel 5420, Frame 729-735)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1933 (Reel 5420, Frame 725-728)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1934 (Reel 5420, Frame 736-749)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1935 (Reel 5420, Frame 750-759)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1936 (Reel 5420, Frame 760-774)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1937 (Reel 5420, Frame 775-784)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1938 (Reel 5420, Frame 785-794)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1939 (Reel 5420, Frame 795-813)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1940 (Reel 5420, Frame 814-828)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1941 (Reel 5420, Frame 829-848)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1942 (Reel 5420, Frame 849-866)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1943 (Reel 5420, Frame 867-879)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1944 (Reel 5420, Frame 880-896)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1945 (Reel 5420, Frame 897-907)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1946 (Reel 5420, Frame 908-919)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1947 (Reel 5420, Frame 920-946)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1948 (Reel 5420, Frame 947-979)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1949 (Reel 5420, Frame 980-1002)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1950 (Reel 5420, Frame 1003-1021)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1951 (Reel 5420, Frame 1022-1039)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1952 (Reel 5420, Frame 1040-1050)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1953 (Reel 5420, Frame 1051-1058)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1954 (Reel 5420, Frame 1059-1071)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1955 (Reel 5420, Frame 1072-1083)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1956 (Reel 5420, Frame 1084-1098)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1957 (Reel 5420, Frame 1099-1110)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1958 (Reel 5420, Frame 1111-1130)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1959 (Reel 5420, Frame 1131-1149)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1960 (Reel 5420, Frame 1150-1176)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1961 (Reel 5420, Frame 1177-1195)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1962 (Reel 5420, Frame 1196-1231)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1963 (Reel 5420, Frame 1232-1254)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1964 (Reel 5420, Frame 1255-1273)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1965 (Reel 5420, Frame 1274-1312)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1966 (Reel 5420, Frame 1313-1332)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1967 (Reel 5420, Frame 1333-1354)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1968 (Reel 5420, Frame 1355-1401)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1969 (Reel 5421, Frame 5-29)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1970 (Reel 5421, Frame 30-53)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1971 (Reel 5421, Frame 54-84)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1972 (Reel 5421, Frame 85-147)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1973 (Reel 5421, Frame 148-165)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1974 (Reel 5421, Frame 166-191)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1975 (Reel 5421, Frame 192-210)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1976 (Reel 5421, Frame 211-239)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1977 (Reel 5421, Frame 240-264)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1978 (Reel 5421, Frame 265-279)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1979 (Reel 5421, Frame 280-285)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1980 (Reel 5421, Frame 286-299)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1981 (Reel 5421, Frame 300-313)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1982 (Reel 5421, Frame 314-326)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1983 (Reel 5421, Frame 327-336)
    - Exhibition catalogs, solo exhibitions, A-Z undated (Reel 5421, Frame 337-446)
    - Exhibition catalogs, group exhibitions, Jan.-Dec., undated (Reel 5421, Frame 447-498)
    - News releases, 1930s (Reel 5421, Frame 499-656)
    - News releases, 1940s (Reel 5421, Frame 657-918)
    - News releases, 1950s (Reel 5421, Frame 919-1097)
    - News releases, 1960s (Reel 5421, Frame 1098-1241)
    - News releases, 1970s (Reel 5421, Frame 1242-1327)
    - News releases, 1980s (Reel 5421, Frame 1328-1357)
    - News releases, [prior to Oct. 1935] (Reel 5421, Frame 1358-1389)
    - News releases, cont., [prior to Oct. 1935] (Reel 5422, Frame 5-47)
    - News releases, [Oct. 1935-1951] (Reel 5422, Frame 48-120)
    - News releases, [1951-1962] (Reel 5422, Frame 121-128)
    - News releases, undated [1962 and later] (Reel 5422, Frame 129-132)
    - Midtown News, 1965-1970 (Reel 5422, Frame 133-140)
    - Miscellaneous Midtown Printed Matter, 1943-1970, undated (Reel 5422, Frame 141-195)
  - Clippings, Artist Files, 7.2:
    Most, but not all, artists included here were affiliated with Midtown Galleries. Files include printed matter comprising mainly clippings, but also tear sheets, exhibition notices, and catalogs from galleries other than Midtown. Files are arranged A-Z with each file in rough chronological order.
    - Adler, M. H. (Reel 5422, Frame 198-200)
    - Aldrich, M. Azzi (Reel 5422, Frame 201-214)
    - Avery, Milton (Reel 5422, Frame 215-218)
    - Avery, Milton, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 638-649)
    - Bartle, Annette (Reel 5422, Frame 219-239)
    - Belle, Cecile (Reel 5422, Frame 240-252)
    - Berman, Saul (see: Saul)
    - Bermingham, Debra (Reel 5437, Frame 650-667)
    - Betts, Edward (Reel 5422, Frame 253-309)
    - Betts, Edward, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 668-677)
    - Billings, Henry (Reel 5422, Frame 310-328)
    - Binford, Julien (Reel 5422, Frame 329-397)
    - Bishop, Isabel (Reel 5422, Frame 398-789)
    - Bishop, Isabel, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 678-860)
    - Block, Henry (Reel 5422, Frame 790-792)
    - Boss, Homer (Reel 5422, Frame 793-811)
    - Brooks, James (Reel 5422, Frame 812-814)
    - Browne, Byron (Reel 5422, Frame 815-818)
    - Cadmus, Paul (Reel 5422, Frame 819-906)
    - Cadmus, Paul, cont. (Reel 5423, Frame 5-314)
    - Cadmus, Paul, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 861-906)
    - Citron, Minna (Reel 5423, Frame 315-335)
    - Clark, Mrs. Dane (Reel 5422, Frame 336-338)
    - Cobb, Ruth (Reel 5422, Frame 339-347)
    - Coiner, Charles (Reel 5422, Frame 348-379)
    - Coiner, Charles, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 918-961)
    - Corcos, Lucille (Reel 5423, Frame 380-400)
    - Criss, Francis (Reel 5422, Frame 401-408)
    - Currie, Bruce (Reel 5422, Frame 409-419)
    - Custer, Bernardine (Reel 5422, Frame 420-443)
    - Davies, Arthur B. (Reel 5437, Frame 915-917)
    - Davis, Floyd M. (Reel 5423, Frame 444-483)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore (Reel 5423, Frame 484-561)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 918-961)
    - De Groot, Adelaide (Reel 5423, Frame 562-572)
    - Dehner, Walt (Reel 5423, Frame 573-575)
    - Dolnick, Beej (Reel 5423, Frame 576-581)
    - Drennan, Vincent (Reel 5423, Frame 582-584)
    - Eby, Kerr (Reel 5423, Frame 585-587)
    - Eilshemius, Louis M. (Reel 5423, Frame 588-595)
    - Esner, Arthur (Reel 5423, Frame 596-600)
    - Etnier, Stephen (Reel 5423, Frame 601-635)
    - Etting, Emlen (Reel 5423, Frame 636-886)
    - Etting, Emlen, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 962-1012)
    - Evergood, Philip (Reel 5423, Frame 887-934)
    - Ferber, Herbert (Reel 5423, Frame 935-948)
    - Fiene, Ernest (Reel 5423, Frame 949-1024)
    - Fitch, Eugene C. (Reel 5423, Frame 1025-1028)
    - Freedman, Maurice (Reel 5423, Frame 1029-1106)
    - Freedman, Maurice, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 1012-1124)
    - French, Jared (Reel 5437, Frame 637)
    - Glinsky, Vincent (Reel 5423, Frame 1107-1110)
    - Goodman, Bertram (Reel 5423, Frame 1111-1113)
    - Greene, Stephen (Reel 5423, Frame 1114-1119)
    - Gregory, Waylande (Reel 5423, Frame 1120-1123)
    - Gross, Chaim (Reel 5423, Frame 1124-1127)
    - Guston, Philip (Reel 5423, Frame 1128-1309)
    - Hale, Nathan Cabot (Reel 5423, Frame 1310-1400)
    - Hale, Nathan Cabot, cont. (Reel 5424, Frame 5-114)
    - Harkavy, Minna (Reel 5424, Frame 115-216)
    - Haskell, Ernest (Reel 5424, Frame 217-220)
    - Hicks, William (Reel 5424, Frame 221-224)
    - Hine, Eleanor (Reel 5424, Frame 225-229)
    - Howland, Isabella (Reel 5424, Frame 230-242)
    - Huntington, Margaret (Reel 5424, Frame 243-256)
    - Hutchinson, Mary (Reel 5424, Frame 257-285)
    - Jones, Joe (Reel 5424, Frame 286-289)
    - Karp, Leon (Reel 5424, Frame 290-319)
    - Katz, Ethel (Reel 5424, Frame 320-321)
    - Kester, Lenard (Reel 5424, Frame 322-369)
    - Kingman, Dong (Reel 5424, Frame 370-1062)
    - Kingman, Dong, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 1125-1198)
    - Kingman, Dong, cont. (Reel 5424, Frame 1063-1345)
    - Koerner, Henry (Reel 5425, Frame 5-29)
    - Koerner, Henry (Reel 5437, Frame 1199-1210)
    - Kraemer, Alfred (Reel 5425, Frame 30-38)
    - Kuhn, Charles (Reel 5425, Frame 39-41)
    - Lahm, Reneé (Reel 5425, Frame 42-78)
    - Laning, Edward (Reel 5425, Frame 79-142)
    - Lehman, Irving (Reel 5425, Frame 143-145)
    - Lenssen, Heidi (Reel 5425, Frame 146-148)
    - Levitz, Jack (Reel 5425, Frame 149-151)
    - Libby, Mark Forrester (Reel 5438, Frame 1067-1096)
    - Lopez, Albert Varga (Reel 5425, Frame 152-154)
    - Loran, Erle (Reel 5425, Frame 155-158)
    - Palmer, William C. (Reel 5427, Frame 26-270)
    - Palmer, William C., cont. (Reel 5438, Frame 249-272)
    - Parsons, Betty (Reel 5427, Frame 271-284)
    - Peirce, Alzira (Reel 5427, Frame 285-373)
    - Peirce, Waldo (Reel 5425, Frame 159-706)
    - Peirce, Waldo, cont. (Reel 5427, Frame 374-926)
    - Peirce, Waldo, cont. (Reel 5438, Frame 273-410)
    - Poor, Henry Varnum (Reel 5425, Frame 707-721)
    - Puccinelli, Raimondo (Reel 5425, Frame 722-757)
    - Reinhardt, Siegfried (Reel 5425, Frame 758-817)
    - Reiss, Lionel (Reel 5425, Frame 818-825)
    - Rembski, Stanislav (Reel 5425, Frame 826-829)
    - Rockmore, Noel (Reel 5425, Frame 830-833)
    - Rosenthal, Doris (Reel 5425, Frame 834-1254)
    - Rosenthal, Doris, cont. (Reel 5438, Frame 411-434)
    - Saarinen, Lilian Swann (Reel 5425, Frame 1255-1272)
    - Saul [Berman] (Reel 5425, Frame 1273-1285)
    - Scharl, Josef (Reel 5425, Frame 1286-1288)
    - Schippert, Elizabeth (Reel 5425, Frame 1289-1292)
    - Schein, Eugenie (Reel 5425, Frame 1293-1298)
    - Schoener, Jason (Reel 5425, Frame 1299-1350)
    - Schweitzer, Gertrude (Reel 5425, Frame 1251-1368)
    - Sepeshy, Zoltan (Reel 5425, Frame 1369-1378)
    - Sepeshy, Zoltan, cont. (Reel 5426, Frame 5-479)
    - Shellhase, George (Reel 5475, Frame 75-77)
    - Shulkin, Anatol (Reel 5438, Frame 435-440)
    - Shulkin, Anatol, cont. (Reel 5475, Frame 1-74)
    - Simkhovitch, Simka (Reel 5475, Frame 78-154)
    - Simpson, Martha (Reel 5475, Frame 155-172)
    - Singer, Susi (Reel 5475, Frame 173-178)
    - Siquieros, David Alfaro (Reel 5475, Frame 179-184)
    - Sivard, Robert (Reel 5475, Frame 185-214)
    - Smith, Jacob Getlar (Reel 5475, Frame 215-293)
    - Sokole, Miron (Reel 5475, Frame 294-367)
    - Sokole, Miron, cont. (Reel 5438, Frame 441-446)
    - Soyer, Isaac (Reel 5475, Frame 368-497)
    - Spagna, Vincent (Reel 5475, Frame 498-523)
    - Stewart, Robert (Reel 5475, Frame 524-526)
    - Stillman, Ary (Reel 5438, Frame 441-446)
    - Stillman, Ary, cont. (Reel 5475, Frame 527-571)
    - Taubes, Frederic (Reel 5475, Frame 572-757)
    - Thon, William (Reel 5438, Frame 485-542)
    - Thon, William, cont. (Reel 5475, Frame 758-1067)
    - Varga, Margit (Reel 5475, Frame 1069-1115)
    - Vickrey, Robert (Reel 5475, Frame 1116-1278)
    - Vukovic, Marko (Reel 5475, Frame 1279-1282)
    - Wiltz, Arnold (Reel 5475, Frame 1283-1312)
    - Wingate, Arline (Reel 5475, Frame 1313-1403)
    - Wolfson, Paula (Reel 5475, Frame 1404-1413)
    - Young, E. Helen (Reel 5475, Frame 1414-1422)
  - Clippings of Midtown Gallery Exhibitions, A-Z, 1932-1982, undated, 7.3: